The first independent film to have successfully
licensed original Beatles recordings.
Good Ol' Freda is a music, documentary, history film directed by Ryan White.
The story of Freda Kelly, a shy Liverpudlian teenager asked to work for
a young local band hoping to make it big: The Beatles.
Their loyal secretary from beginning to end, Freda tells
her tales for the first time in 50 years.
Self, played by Freda Kelly.
Self, played by Tony Barrow.
Self, played by Billy Hatton.
Self, played by Ringo Starr.
Self (archive footage), played by John Lennon.
Self (archive footage), played by Paul McCartney.
Freda Kelly (born 14 July 1945) is an Irish secretary who was employed by the Beatles and their manager,
Brian Epstein, from 1962 until 1972 and was secretary of the group's official fan club.
Kelly worked with the band as they rose from local popularity to
world-wide fame and through their dissolution.
A 2013 documentary, Good Ol' Freda, chronicled Kelly's ten-plus
year association with the group and its members.
The film explores themes of musical, secretary, rock band.